[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Did Dr. Murray ever mention to you having administered Propofol to Michael Jackson?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Dr.", "Murray", "ever", "mention", "to", "you", "having", "administered", "Propofol", "to", "Michael", "Jackson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "No, he did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Did Conrad Murray ever mention the word Propofol to you during the time that you were at the location or in his presence?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Conrad", "Murray", "ever", "mention", "the", "word", "Propofol", "to", "you", "during", "the", "time", "that", "you", "were", "at", "the", "location", "or", "in", "his", "presence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "No, he did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What would he make of all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "make", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I haven't seen any of the trial.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "seen", "any", "of", "the", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "I mean, notwithstanding that, do you still feel slightly damaged by the whole process of stardom for so long?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "notwithstanding", "that", ",", "do", "you", "still", "feel", "slightly", "damaged", "by", "the", "whole", "process", "of", "stardom", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I'm more damaged -- I feel more damaged now than I ever remember feeling as a child.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "more", "damaged", "--", "I", "feel", "more", "damaged", "now", "than", "I", "ever", "remember", "feeling", "as", "a", "child", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Really, why?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Because I was a kid, and I also had a lot of fun, and a lot of opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "was", "a", "kid", ",", "and", "I", "also", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "fun", ",", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Why do you feel damaged now?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "feel", "damaged", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Because I'm -- because in a way, I was so protected, and I was so naive, I was sort of -- I maintained a level of naivete for so long that now when I see things, the way the business is, the way the industry is, the way the world is, I'm so much more affected by it, because I can't believe -- I always say I hate people, you know, because I'm not -- I did not get hardened by it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "--", "because", "in", "a", "way", ",", "I", "was", "so", "protected", ",", "and", "I", "was", "so", "naive", ",", "I", "was", "sort", "of", "--", "I", "maintained", "a", "level", "of", "naivete", "for", "so", "long", "that", "now", "when", "I", "see", "things", ",", "the", "way", "the", "business", "is", ",", "the", "way", "the", "industry", "is", ",", "the", "way", "the", "world", "is", ",", "I", "'m", "so", "much", "more", "affected", "by", "it", ",", "because", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "--", "I", "always", "say", "I", "hate", "people", ",", "you", "know", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "did", "not", "get", "hardened", "by", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is this very similar, do you think, to the way Michael Jackson probably felt?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "very", "similar", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "the", "way", "Michael", "Jackson", "probably", "felt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I think -- we talked about it a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "we", "talked", "about", "it", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "How do you feel about your own children going into any sort of fame?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "your", "own", "children", "going", "into", "any", "sort", "of", "fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "I pray to God that they don't want to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "pray", "to", "God", "that", "they", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Listening.", "answer_tokens": ["Listening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "What do you make of what's happening to your country in terms of so many people now out of work, suffering financial problems?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "to", "your", "country", "in", "terms", "of", "so", "many", "people", "now", "out", "of", "work", ",", "suffering", "financial", "problems", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "It's devastating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "devastating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Are you a fan of President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "of", "President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "When, in fact, you got a great brain?", "question_tokens": ["When", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "you", "got", "a", "great", "brain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Should it matter?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "it", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Here's the thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Coming up -- sorry?", "question_tokens": ["Coming", "up", "--", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", ":", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Beer, next.", "answer_tokens": ["Beer", ",", "next", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "You want a beer?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "a", "beer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Not now, I want one from your pub.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "now", ",", "I", "want", "one", "from", "your", "pub", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Horrible memories?", "question_tokens": ["Horrible", "memories", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Incredibly warm and happy memories for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Incredibly", "warm", "and", "happy", "memories", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "But you were good?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "were", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I was pretty good, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "pretty", "good", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "You were a hot athlete in your day?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "a", "hot", "athlete", "in", "your", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I was a good catcher.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "a", "good", "catcher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Not true?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Do you like the fact that you have this slightly intimidating reputation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "have", "this", "slightly", "intimidating", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I don't like or dislike it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "like", "or", "dislike", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Do you think America needs somebody like you who's going to be tough?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "America", "needs", "somebody", "like", "you", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "tough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think America needs lots of tough people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "America", "needs", "lots", "of", "tough", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJS", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "If you were being honest, what do you think your mother would have said were your best qualities, and what would she say would be your not-so-good qualities?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "being", "honest", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "your", "mother", "would", "have", "said", "were", "your", "best", "qualities", ",", "and", "what", "would", "she", "say", "would", "be", "your", "not-so-good", "qualities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I think if -- the best quality she would say is brutally honest, tough, and compassionate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "--", "the", "best", "quality", "she", "would", "say", "is", "brutally", "honest", ",", "tough", ",", "and", "compassionate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Can we hold you to that, Governor?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "hold", "you", "to", "that", ",", "Governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Yes, you can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Is that one of those little jokes where you think, hang on, maybe I went too far there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "one", "of", "those", "little", "jokes", "where", "you", "think", ",", "hang", "on", ",", "maybe", "I", "went", "too", "far", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, listen, my wife didn't like the jokes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "my", "wife", "did", "n't", "like", "the", "jokes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Why wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Because that's not the way you make decisions like running for president of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "'s", "not", "the", "way", "you", "make", "decisions", "like", "running", "for", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 380, "question": "ORGAN: Why aren't you ready?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Why", "are", "n't", "you", "ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Listen, I've been governor for --", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "governor", "for", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "How old are you now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I'm 48.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "48", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "You're a straight talker, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "straight", "talker", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Can you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "You're wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Are you 100 percent certain you won't run in 2016?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "100", "percent", "certain", "you", "wo", "n't", "run", "in", "2016", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "There are so many variables to that, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "so", "many", "variables", "to", "that", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "You were always a bit of a high flyer here -- president of everything, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "always", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "high", "flyer", "here", "--", "president", "of", "everything", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Senior class, junior class, sophomore class -- yes, all the way through.", "answer_tokens": ["Senior", "class", ",", "junior", "class", ",", "sophomore", "class", "--", "yes", ",", "all", "the", "way", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Can you divorce being a Catholic with all that that means and all you stand for as a Catholic -- and I'm a Catholic -- from running for high office?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "divorce", "being", "a", "Catholic", "with", "all", "that", "that", "means", "and", "all", "you", "stand", "for", "as", "a", "Catholic", "--", "and", "I", "'m", "a", "Catholic", "--", "from", "running", "for", "high", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "WDT", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ":", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "HRISTIE: Well, I think that you have to understand that we are not a religious democracy.", "answer_tokens": ["HRISTIE", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "you", "have", "to", "understand", "that", "we", "are", "not", "a", "religious", "democracy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "homosexuality", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, my religion says it's a sin.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "religion", "says", "it", "'s", "a", "sin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Can you see a situation where you would change your mind about that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "see", "a", "situation", "where", "you", "would", "change", "your", "mind", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Obviously in light of Weiner-gate, Schwarzenegger-gate, and so on, is there anything you want to get off your chest?", "question_tokens": ["Obviously", "in", "light", "of", "Weiner-gate", ",", "Schwarzenegger-gate", ",", "and", "so", "on", ",", "is", "there", "anything", "you", "want", "to", "get", "off", "your", "chest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "You don't look like a priest to me, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "look", "like", "a", "priest", "to", "me", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Well, should we be ever worried about any skeletons tumbling out of the Christie closet?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "should", "we", "be", "ever", "worried", "about", "any", "skeletons", "tumbling", "out", "of", "the", "Christie", "closet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "You know, listen, any confessions I need to make, I'll make to my wife and to my priest, not on CNN to you, pal.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "listen", ",", "any", "confessions", "I", "need", "to", "make", ",", "I", "'ll", "make", "to", "my", "wife", "and", "to", "my", "priest", ",", "not", "on", "CNN", "to", "you", ",", "pal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Do you ever feel guilty about stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "feel", "guilty", "about", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Listen, I had a Sicilian mother.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "had", "a", "Sicilian", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What do you feel most guilty about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "most", "guilty", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "It depends on the day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", "the", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes, because I'm really struggling, been struggling for a long time with it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "really", "struggling", ",", "been", "struggling", "for", "a", "long", "time", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Why do you think you've had a battle with your weight?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "had", "a", "battle", "with", "your", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "If I could figure it out, I'd fix it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "figure", "it", "out", ",", "I", "'d", "fix", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "You don't know what it is?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Do you ever get help for it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "get", "help", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Sure, plenty of times.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "plenty", "of", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Where do you fall down in terms of dealing with it?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "fall", "down", "in", "terms", "of", "dealing", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I eat too much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "eat", "too", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Is it -- is it the one jibe about you that really stings?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "the", "one", "jibe", "about", "you", "that", "really", "stings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "HRISTIE: No.", "answer_tokens": ["HRISTIE", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Final question for here, do you think you would make a good president?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", "for", "here", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "would", "make", "a", "good", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "You know, my wife was asked this question and she said yes.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "my", "wife", "was", "asked", "this", "question", "and", "she", "said", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "How much of your life have you spent in places like this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "your", "life", "have", "you", "spent", "in", "places", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "A lot, especially when I was running for office.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", ",", "especially", "when", "I", "was", "running", "for", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Other than nice food and coffee?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "nice", "food", "and", "coffee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "It was a place to socialize for teenagers, a place where we could come.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "place", "to", "socialize", "for", "teenagers", ",", "a", "place", "where", "we", "could", "come", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "It's OK.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Is that the New Jersey way?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "New", "Jersey", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Why are you looking at me that way?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "looking", "at", "me", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "You know, it's -- we're still evaluating you, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "we", "'re", "still", "evaluating", "you", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Is that an accurate description?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "accurate", "description", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "No, I think we're more of a team than one person wearing the trousers.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "more", "of", "a", "team", "than", "one", "person", "wearing", "the", "trousers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I definitely think I'm a good woman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "think", "I", "'m", "a", "good", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Yes, I'd agree with that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'d", "agree", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "What if your country needs him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "your", "country", "needs", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Well, I'm sure his country could use him but his family needs him too.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "his", "country", "could", "use", "him", "but", "his", "family", "needs", "him", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "What is it about him, do you think, that if it came to it, if it came to a presidential race, why should Americans vote for him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "him", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "if", "it", "came", "to", "it", ",", "if", "it", "came", "to", "a", "presidential", "race", ",", "why", "should", "Americans", "vote", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "NNPS", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Because Chris has an -- an unbelievable ability to succinctly analyze a problem, come up with solutions, listen to people and then communicate the solutions.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "Chris", "has", "an", "--", "an", "unbelievable", "ability", "to", "succinctly", "analyze", "a", "problem", ",", "come", "up", "with", "solutions", ",", "listen", "to", "people", "and", "then", "communicate", "the", "solutions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Anything you want to share with us?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "you", "want", "to", "share", "with", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "What's the single biggest misconception about your husband, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "single", "biggest", "misconception", "about", "your", "husband", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Probably that he's mean.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "that", "he", "'s", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "He's the nicest, most ferocious prosecutor you've ever met, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "the", "nicest", ",", "most", "ferocious", "prosecutor", "you", "'ve", "ever", "met", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "But he's a really good person.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "he", "'s", "a", "really", "good", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Bit of a pussycat really?", "question_tokens": ["Bit", "of", "a", "pussycat", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Wouldn't go that far?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "go", "that", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "You're putting words into my mouth, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "putting", "words", "into", "my", "mouth", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "How did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "No, I mean, I -- I really was just happy that he coming to the game.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "--", "I", "really", "was", "just", "happy", "that", "he", "coming", "to", "the", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Now, are you happy if that helicopter comes into sight again in the middle of the game?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "are", "you", "happy", "if", "that", "helicopter", "comes", "into", "sight", "again", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "the", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Maybe -- maybe it was a good intimidation tactic.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "--", "maybe", "it", "was", "a", "good", "intimidation", "tactic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Well, you are at an age -- how old are you now?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "are", "at", "an", "age", "--", "how", "old", "are", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Seventeen.", "answer_tokens": ["Seventeen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "When you look -- are you a Republican by nature, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "--", "are", "you", "a", "Republican", "by", "nature", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "When you look at the other candidates doesn't part of you think, wow, wish the old man would run, because he'd have a better chance?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "the", "other", "candidates", "does", "n't", "part", "of", "you", "think", ",", "wow", ",", "wish", "the", "old", "man", "would", "run", ",", "because", "he", "'d", "have", "a", "better", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "Well, you know, I -- I guess part of me thinks that, a little bit, but I -- I don't think for us personally as a family and for him it would be the best idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "guess", "part", "of", "me", "thinks", "that", ",", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "but", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "for", "us", "personally", "as", "a", "family", "and", "for", "him", "it", "would", "be", "the", "best", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "When he says that, he means it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "says", "that", ",", "he", "means", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Because I ask him that all the time too.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "ask", "him", "that", "all", "the", "time", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Why would you keep having to ask him if -- if when he says it, you believe him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "keep", "having", "to", "ask", "him", "if", "--", "if", "when", "he", "says", "it", ",", "you", "believe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Well, I just want to be sure, because I just don't want him to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "be", "sure", ",", "because", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "want", "him", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Would you like him to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "Sarah, why are you concerned about it?", "question_tokens": ["Sarah", ",", "why", "are", "you", "concerned", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "I just want him to be healthy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "want", "him", "to", "be", "healthy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Finally, you two, what would you say are the best things about your dad and the most annoying?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "you", "two", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "are", "the", "best", "things", "about", "your", "dad", "and", "the", "most", "annoying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "CD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "The best things.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "I'll bet he's a nightmare isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "bet", "he", "'s", "a", "nightmare", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "He told me that -- in the campaign, I'd asked if I was going to have to have state police with me all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "told", "me", "that", "--", "in", "the", "campaign", ",", "I", "'d", "asked", "if", "I", "was", "going", "to", "have", "to", "have", "state", "police", "with", "me", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]